本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
我们是宝石战士
We are the Crystal Gems
终日拯救世界
we'll always save the day
■
时间轴： Enpistu
如果你感到怀疑
and if you think we can't
我们总能找到出路
we'll always find a way
■
翻译： Tracy  阿拱
所以全世界人们都信任
that's why the people of this world believe in...
■
校订： violin1443  Enpistu
石榴  紫晶  和珍珠  还有史蒂文
Garnet, Amethyst...and Pearl...and Steven!
宇宙小子  第一季第十五  十六集
Steven Universe  S01E15E16  Onion Trade/Steven the Sword Fighter
洋葱头的交换
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
-紫晶  -在外面呢  老弟
- Amethyst! - Outside, dude.
-你看见游侠小子了么  -什么
- Have you seen ranger guy? - Excuse me?
游侠小子  我的小子们中的一员
Ranger guy. One of my guys.
你知道吧 "小子们"
You know... Guys?
小子们
G.U.Y.S.!
您眼皮底下的小子
"Guys Under Your Supervision."
我们有忍者小子  建筑小子  警察小子
There's ninja guy, construction guy, cop guy,
眼睛小子  隐形小子
Eye guy, invisible guy,
锯齿小子  猫咪小子  苹果小子
jagged guy, cat guy, apple guy,
其中最重要的就是游侠小子  他是最棒的小子
and my main man ranger guy, the best of all the guys.
他不见了
He's gone missing.
你见过他没
Have you seen him?
我听到了什么
What's that I hear?
你没法在自己堆满垃圾的房间里找到小玩偶了吗
You can't find your little men in that super junky room of yours?
也没那么糟啦
It's not that bad.
它是怎么进去的
How'd that get in there?
是你把窗户开着 方便它进出的
You left your window wide open for things to just fly in and out.
算了  放过他吧  珍
Aww, give him a break, P.
虽然我的房间也很乱
My room's messy,
但是我都能找到我要的东西
but I always find what I'm looking for.
那你为什么还没找到我的魔法斧
Then why haven't you found my magic ax?
我只是还没找呢
I haven't looked for it yet.
紫晶  你现在就去找
Amethyst, go and find it right this second.
那你还是自己去找吧
Hey, feel free to go look for it yourself.
我才不进你那个垃圾堆呢
There's no way I'm going into that dump.
珍珠  你唠叨个没完都让史蒂文不开心了
Pearl, all your nagging's made Steven depressed.
-你没事吧  史蒂文  -我没事
- Is everything okay, Steven? - Yeah. I'm fine.
我得去把这个坏消息告诉我爸爸
Just have to break the bad news to my dad.
爸爸  爸爸
Dad! Dad!
-我错了  -你是错了
- I'm so sorry! - Yeah, you're sorry.
竟然不拿水管就进来
Sorry you walked through that door without a hose in your hand,
准备好开战吧
ready for battle!
-等等  -天啊  你看上去又湿又难过
- Wait! - Man, you look sad and wet.
发生了什么事啊  小家伙
What happened to your life, little guy?
我  我丢个了东西
I... lost something.
一个很宝贵的东西
Something precious.
你的童真吗
Your innocence?
我弄丢了游侠小子
I lost ranger guy.
小子之一  还记得去年夏天
One of my guys... from our special day
我们在海滩那个特别的日子吗
at the beach last summer?
他是你在那天晚上买给我的
You bought him for me at the end of the day.
他可特别了  帽子颜色跟原版不一样
He was one of a kind. He had a miscolored hat.
你怎么能不记得了呢
How could you not remember?
那天我们是不是还吃了个特别棒的油炸糕
Was this the same day we ate that awesome funnel cake?
呃  啥
Uh, huh?
没错  那个油炸糕啊
Yeah, man. That funnel cake...
我到现在还留着盘子呢  快来
I even kept the plate. Come on!
好漂亮的气球
Cool balloons.
瞧瞧  这里有罐头  纸巾  一个悠悠球
Uh, let's see here. Got cans, napkins, oh, a yo-yo,
一本悠悠球技巧大全
a book about yo-yo tricks,
一个我找了好久的三明治
a sandwich I've been meaning to catch up on...
嗷  我的屁股
Ow, my butt!
等等  你刚刚说啥来着
Wait. What's your story again?
我最喜欢的游侠小子不见了  所以我很伤心
I lost my special ranger guy, and I'm quite upset over it.
这个嘛  这里有整袋的零钱
Huh. Well... here's a bag full of quarters.
你想要哪个小子尽管去买
Now you can get all the guys you want.
-谢谢  -你说啥
- Thank you. - What did you say?
谢谢
Thank you!
我们很快就要重聚了  游侠小子  来吧
We'll be reunited soon, ranger guy. Here we go.
然后
And...
戴夫小子
Dave guy!
-啥  -好幸运呀
- What?! - Lucky!
一点也不幸运好吗  他是最糟的小子
Not lucky! He's, like, the worst guy.
没准他带着什么好东西呢
Maybe he comes with something cool.
税收
Taxes?
拜托  戴夫小子  这就是你的能耐了吗
Come on, Dave guy! Is this all you have to offer ...
就只有一堆文书工作吗  回答我啊
a bunch of paperwork? Answer me!
谢天谢地我还有很多零钱
Thank goodness I have all these qauarters.
戴夫小子
Dave guy!
不是吧
No!
戴夫小子
Dave guy!
给我停下
Stop it!
戴夫小子
Dave guy!
我要游侠小子啊
Ranger guy!
这台机器的小子已卖完  请下次再来
This machine is out of guys. Please try again another time.
结束了
It's over.
洋葱头
Huh? Oh. Onion.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
他拿到游侠小子了
He's got a ranger guy?!
洋葱头  等等  我们交换吧
Onion! Wait up! Let's trade!
他去哪边了  看来他要买一个手提箱
Which way did he go? Oh! I guess he needs a suitcase.
他还在跟人家讨价还价
Is he haggling with that guy?
真是个难缠的顾客啊
He's a tough customer.
看来是谈妥了
Looks like they worked something out.
啥  他把人家午饭拿走了
Huh? Did he get that guy's lunch?
我想看看他是要怎么玩
I wonder how this is gonna play out.
哇  看上去就美味
Oh, man. Hey, good looking.
他到底在干嘛
What the heck is he doing?!
他难道都不饿吗
He's not even hungry?!
别扔西红柿啊
Not the tomatoes!
那是洋葱头的爸爸吗
Hey. Is that Onion's dad?
看来他们不需要语言
I guess they don't need words.
啥  这么快就走了
Huh? He's leaving so soon?
洋葱头是在这坐了一整天就为等他的爸爸吗
Does Onion just... sit around and wait for his dad all day?
游侠小子  好吧  我来了
Ranger guy! Okay. Let's do this.
嘿  洋葱头  你好吗
Hey, Onion. How are you?
很好  很好
That's good. That's good.
我不禁注意到你也是一个小子迷
I couldn't help but notice that you're a guys fan.
"小子们"  你知道吧
You know, guys?
就是你背后兜里的人偶
The little man in your back pocket?
对  就是游侠小子
Yeah, ranger guy!
你想不想用那个过气的旧游侠小子
How would you like to trade that boring old ranger guy
来换一个全新的 还没拆封的
for a brand-spanking-new, mint-in-box...
戴夫小子
Dave guy!
很棒是不是
Pretty nice, right?
我明白你的意思了
Oh. I see where this is going.
那就让你占个大便宜
You're getting quite the deal here...
给你两个戴夫小子咯  赞啊
with two Dave guys! Yeah!
啥  还不够吗  再加两个
What? You want more? Like... two more?
再加五个  再加十个
Five more. 10 more?
再加二十个  一整袋都给你
20 more. This whole bag?
三十个戴夫小子换你一个游侠小子
All 30 of these Dave guys for just one ranger guy!
我只有这么多了  机器都空了
But there aren't any more. The machine's empty.
我把它们全都买下了
I bought them all.
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
嘿  咱们再谈谈啊
Hey! Let's work something out.
游侠小子
Ranger guuuuy!
唉  讨厌的戴夫小子
Ugh, stupid Dave guy.
你前途无光  发型恶心  浑身发臭
Got no future, your haircut's gross, you smell bad...
你在说珍珠吗
You talking about Pearl?
不是
No.
我在说又老又蠢的戴夫小子
I'm talking about dumb, old Dave guy.
你自己看吧
I mean, just look at him.
你看他像是有前途的样子吗
Does it look like his life is going anywhere?
饶了他吧
Ah, cut him a break.
没准今年他就会转运呢
Maybe this is the year he gets his life together.
没准他会得到一个很好的实习工作
Maybe he'll get a cool internship.
我表示怀疑
I doubt it.
我用三十个戴夫小子
I can't even trade 30 Dave guys with Onion
都不能从洋葱头那里都换来一个游侠小子
to get one ranger guy!
所以说你需要更多的这种人偶
So, you need more of that little man
来换另外一种人偶
to get some other little man.
是的
Yeah.
但是机器里的都卖光了
And the machine is sold out of them.
-这是啥  -珍珠的复制魔杖
- What is that? - Pearl's replicator wand.
你可以用这玩意儿复制东西
You can use it to make copies of stuff.
你会魔法
You're magic.
我相信你会搞明白怎么用这玩意儿的
I'm sure you can figure out how to use it.
你在这儿坐了一整天
Have you been sitting here all day
这东西就一直在你头发里吗
with this in your hair?
没有啦
Nah.
我起来去找珍珠的傻缺斧头
I got up to look for Pearl's dumb axe
结果却找到了这个
but found that instead.
然后我就用它复制了一堆垃圾
Then I replicated a bunch of garbage
都堆在珍珠的房间里了
and stuffed it all in Pearl's room.
洋葱头
Hey, Onion!
这样就有三十一个了
That makes 31!
你还想要更多  三十二个怎么样
You want more? How about 32?
三十三
33?
三十四  三十五
34? 35?
三十六
36?
三十七  三十八
37? 38?
三十九  四十
39? 40!?
够了  你到底想要什么
Enough! What is it that you want?!
你是想要这个  跟你换游侠小子
You mean... you want this? For ranger guy?
我们正在和游侠小子在海滩上巡逻
We are on the scene with ranger guy on beach patrol.
看来一切都很顺利  史蒂文
Things are looking just great out here, Steven.
是的  一切顺利
Yep. Everything is great.
顺利
Great.
你一直都这么无聊吗  游侠小子
Were you always this boring, ranger guy?
我以前是个医生
I used to be a doctor.
要想玩得开心  或许你身边还得有其他的
Maybe you're just more fun around other ...
小子们
Guys?
戴夫小子  还以为我再也不会看到
Dave guy? I thought I saw the last of ...
发生了  什么
Hey! What's the big i... dea?
洋葱头
Onion!
太荒唐了  他怎么会有我的复制魔杖呢
This is ridiculous. How did he get my replicator?
那孩子不该拥有这东西
That child should not be in possession of such an item.
这不是史蒂文的人偶吗
Aren't these Steven's little men?
他们叫"小子"
They're called "Guys!"
你能给我解释一下吗
Can you please explain this mess?
我用复制魔杖跟他换了游侠小子
I traded that replicator for ranger guy.
史蒂文  你为什么不直接复制一个游侠小子呢
Steven, why didn't you just replicate ranger guy?
该死的
Dang it!
在情况变得更糟之前赶紧出手吧
Let's go before this gets any worse.
喔  怎样才能在这些东西里活动自如啊
Whoa! Uh. How do you move in this stuff?
（注：指《唐老鸭俱乐部》里的史高治·麦克老鸭  史高治有在金库里游泳的能力）
试着当只有钱的鸭子就行
Try and act like a rich duck.
什么意思
What does that mean?
我的天  我只是想来点冰淇淋而已
Oh, my gosh! I just wanted some ice cream.
-你好  格雷格  -到底发生了什么事
- Hi, Greg. - What the heck is going on out here?
就是  我们的日常嘛
Uh, you know, just doing our thing.
交给我  它不属于你
Hand it over. It doesn't belong to you.
这不是游戏
This is not a game.
他射中了什么
What did he shoot?
快下去
Go under!
至少没有玩具掉下来了
At least it stopped raining toys.
不好  快装作有钱的鸭子
Ah! Rich duck!
洋葱头
Ooooonion!
洋葱头  快停下  我们再换回来吧
Onion, please stop. Let's trade back.
游侠小子还给你  他最棒了
You take ranger guy. He's the best.
他还戴着一顶串色的帽
He even has a miscolored h...
这是我的游侠小子
This is my ranger guy!
你用我自己的小子跟我交换
You traded me my own guy!
我们的交换不算数
Our trade didn't count.
那不管用啊
That didn't work.
我再也不借紫晶任何东西了
I'm never letting Amethyst borrow anything again.
石榴
Garnet!
我才不想收拾这烂摊子
I'm not cleaning up this mess.
我想明白你为什么拿了我的游侠小子了  洋葱头
I think I understand why you took my ranger guy, Onion.
我猜你在等你爸爸的时候一定很孤单吧
I bet you get pretty lonely waiting for you dad all day.
你肯定也很无聊
You were probably really bored, too.
因为你想你爸爸了  所以拿走了我的游侠小子
And 'cause you missed your dad, you took my ranger guy,
因为它象征着我和我爸爸的亲情
which is a symbol of the relationship I have with my dad.
不是吗  只有第一条吗
No? Just the first thing?
好吧  给你
Well, here.
你比我更需要他
You need him more than I do.
我们走吧
Let's go.
所以那些复制品就彻底消失了吗
So, all the stuff that got copied turned into nothing?
-没错  -没劲
- Yep. - Rats.
你刚才做得很棒
That was really cool what you did back there.
谢谢  爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
你为了个玩具就要弄出这么大麻烦吗
But you went through all that trouble for a toy?
它不只是个玩具啦  那其中还有好多回忆
It was more about the memories than the toy.
现在我们有新的回忆了
Now we have new memories ...
非常糟糕的回忆
horrible, horrible memories.
剑客史蒂文
是你
是你杀死了我哥哥
是你让我永远孤独作战
孤独战士  你太孤单了
Oh, Lonely Blade, you so lonely.
就你这种货色也能打败我吗
本大人乃是影子武士集团的首领
什么  扫地僧竟然是邪恶的武士首领
What?! The janitor is the evil samurai president?!
可真够疯狂的
That's bananas.
拜托  这不明摆着么
Oh, come on. It was so obvious.
一有打斗  他就藏在暗处拖地
He's been mopping in the background of every fight scene.
你看  盒子封面上也有他
Look. Here he is on the cover of the box.
真的耶
Oh, yeah!
为了我的荣誉和我的哥哥
我要击败你
看我飞剑
回旋
撕裂千影声
破
加油  孤独武士  加油啊
Go, Lonely, go!
再来一招飞剑回旋
Do the boomerang blade again!
拜托
Oh, come on.
这实在是可笑  瞧瞧他们的动作
This is ridiculous. Just look at their form.
这根本不是真正的剑术
This is nothing like real sword-fighting.
嘘
Shh!
只是部电影嘛  珍珠
It's just a movie, Pearl.
如果你想见识一下真正的剑术
Well, if you ever want to see a demonstration of proper sword techniques,
我很乐意给你露一手
I'd be happy to show you.
现在吗
Now?
那么  为了展示真正的剑术
All right. In order to give a proper demonstration,
我需要一个陪练对象
I'm going to need a sparring partner.
幸运的是  我这里就有一位绝佳的陪练
Luckily, I have the perfect candidate right here.
-酷  全息的珍珠  -我天
- Cool! Hologram Pearl! - Ah, geez.
您想参加决斗吗
Do you wish to engage in combat?
让我们来一场十分完美的决斗
Let this be the perfect battle.
来挑战我你就已经大错特错了
You've already made a mistake by challenging me.
还是让我们用剑来说话吧
We shall let our swords decide.
傻死了
Nerd!
-嘘  -嘘
- Shh! - Shh!
决斗开始
Commencing duel.
防御等级S  目前零破绽
Defense rank "S." Zero openings detected.
-加油  珍珠  加油  -加油  全息珍珠
- Go, Pearl, go! - Go, Holo-Pearl!
发现破绽
Opening detected.
比赛结束  挑战者胜利
Match set. Challenger wins!
太棒了  珍珠
Whoo-hoo! Yay, Pearl!
你想再来一场吗
Do you wish to battle again?
珍珠  太不可思议啦  你太酷啦
Pearl! That was amazing! You were so cool!
那个嘛  人总是尽力而为的嘛
Oh, well. One does try their best.
你能不能教我剑术格斗  就像你一样
Will you teach me to sword-fight like you?
可以  但我们应该从基础练起
All right, but we should start with the basics.
开启训练模式
Initiate training mode.
训练模式已开启  第一关  开始
Training mode initiated. Level 1. Begin!
靠后站  史蒂文  记得仔细看我的招式
I want you to stand back, Steven, and watch me carefully, okay?
躲  闪  刺
Parry! Parry! Thrust!
看到我的步伐了吗  史蒂文
Do you see what I'm doing with my feet, Steven?
躲  闪  刺
Parry! Parry! Thrust!
看好我是怎么保持重心的
Notice where I keep my center of gravity.
呃  你能教我些酷炫的技法吗
Aww. Can you show me something cool,
就像飞剑回旋
like the boomerang blade?
史蒂文  你要明白那可不是真正的剑术
Steven, you know that's not a real sword technique.
飞剑回旋  飞剑回旋
Boomerang blade! Boomerang blade!
飞剑回旋
Boomerang blade!
史蒂文  这些才是真正的剑术
Steven, these are real sword techniques,
可不是电影里那些愚蠢的大招
not those silly things from your movie.
我们需要耐心等待最佳时刻来
It's about waiting carefully for the perfect moment to ...
刺
Thrust!
-我天  -不
- Whoa. - Oh, no.
-珍珠  -天哪
- Pearl? - Whoopsy-daisy.
没事的  史蒂文  我不会有事
Steven, it's okay. I'm gonna be just ...
不要  珍珠  珍珠
No! Pearl? Pearl!
挑战者失败  第一关失败
Challenger defeated! Level 1 failed.
-史蒂文  -史蒂文
- Steven! - Steven!
我  我只是  她本来想
I-I was just ... and ... and she was trying to ...
没事的  史蒂文  珍珠她不要紧的
Steven, it's okay. Pearl's gonna be just fine.
什么意思
What do you mean?
有时候  如果我们的身体被损坏
Sometimes if our bodies are badly damaged,
我们的身体形态就会消失
we release our physical forms
退化为宝石态然后复生
and retreat to our gems to regenerate.
-就是说  她会没事对吗  -不要担心  伙计
- So, she's gonna be okay? - Don't worry, bud.
这种事儿也不稀罕  我经常会这样
This kind of thing just happens sometimes ... usually to me.
一直是你
Always to you.
嘿  我比较热血嘛
Hey, I'm scrappy.
还能怎么样呢
What do you want?
那她多久才会变回来呀
So, how long will it take her to regenerate ...
五分钟吗  十分钟吗
5 minutes, 10 minutes?
两周后
-为什么这么长时间啊  -你好吗
- What's taking so long? - What up?
-你好  -她还没恢复
- He-e-ey. - She's still not done?
老天  这事她就不慌不忙了
Man, she's really taking her time with this one.
不过老实说  我喜欢你把这里搞成这样子
Got to tell you, though, love what you've done with the place.
-珍珠总是帮我收拾屋子  -还是拉倒吧
- Pearl usually helps me tidy up. - Ah, I say leave it.
如果真正的珍珠不在这儿
Hey, if real Pearl can't be here,
我们可以退求其次嘛
there's always the next best thing!
你想参加决斗吗
Do you wish to engage in combat?
史蒂文  把那个东西盖上吧
Steven, cover that thing back up.
可它可像珍珠啦  你瞧
But it's like Pearl! Look at it!
是吗
Ye-e-e-ah.
这可不是珍珠
That ain't Pearl.
好吧  也许我能让它表现得更像珍珠
Well, maybe I can get it to act like her.
这个是  一团糟
Here we have... A mess.
收拾东西是珍珠最喜欢的爱好之一
Organizing messes is one of Pearl's favorite hobbies.
看  珍珠喜欢把它们按照类型排列
Here. Pearl likes to organize them by type ...
比如动物类  人形类  杂七杂八类
animal, humanoid, miscellaneous.
现在你试试
Now you try.
你拔剑也没用
You've drawn your sword in vain!
什么
What?! Aah!
挑战者失败
Challenger defeated!
也许我们该试试其他的
Maybe we need to try something else.
-我可开始啦  -随你吧
- I'm gonna do it. - Go on, then.
每次紫晶做些这种有趣儿的事
Pearl always likes to tease Amethyst
珍珠就爱调侃她
when she does funny stuff like this.
这次我不会轻易放过你
I won't go easy on you this time!
对就是那种态度
That's the spirit!
你们这些淘气鬼在这儿做什么
What are you rascals doing over here?
拿起你的武器吧  挑战者
Draw your weapon, challenger!
史蒂文  你怎么还在和那个东西瞎逛
Ugh. Steven, why are you still hanging out with that thing?
恶心死啦
It's gross.
我真的很想念和珍珠在一起的日子
I just really miss spending time with Pearl.
珍珠迟早会回来的  史蒂文  耐心点
Pearl will come back to us in time, Steven. Have patience.
还有别和那东西一块逛了  怪瘆人的
And stop hanging out with that thing. It's creepy.
你喜欢走木板小道  对吧
You had fun at the boardwalk, right?
躲
Parry!
拜托  你必须得配合我啊
Aw, come on. You got to work with me here.
这是珍珠最喜欢的树
This is Pearl's favorite tree.
你不认识它了吗
Don't you recognize it?
你在想什么呢
What's on your mind?
说说吧  不要藏着掖着了
Come on. Don't hold back.
(注：hold back也有"退缩"的意思）
接受挑战
Challenge accepted!
什么
What?!
不要啊  树倒了
Oh, no! The tree!
挑战者失败
Challenger defeated!
真正的珍珠永远不会那么做的
Real Pearl would never do that!
你没救了
Rah! You're hopeless!
离我远点
Get away from me!
珍珠  你还没回来真是太遗憾了
It's too bad you're still not back, Pearl,
我刚找到了孤独武士第五部的影碟
because I just found a copy of the fifth "Lonely Blade" Movie!
你还让要我等多久呢  珍珠
How long are you gonna make me wait, Pearl?
爆米花好了  呆这儿别动哦
Oh, the popcorn's done. Stay right there.
你想测试自己的技能  和我对决吗
Do you wish to test your skills against me in a duel?!
不  别再提剑术决斗了
No! No sword-fighting!
拔出你的剑  完成使命吧
Draw your sword and fulfill your destiny!
才不  别再烦我和真正的珍珠了
Huh? No! Leave real Pearl and me alone!
回你的布下面凉快去
Go back under your sheet.
是你吗  哥哥
Brother, is that you?
没错  正是我
Yes, it's me ...
我是你的哥哥
your...brother.
你的剑术
Your technique is...
哇  这配音真的好棒
Whoa! This dub is really good.
你觉得呢  珍珠
What do you think, Pearl?
躲
Parry!
弟弟
Brother!
等等
Just wait a minute.
你根本不是我的亲哥哥
You're not my real brother!
飞剑回旋
Aah! Boomerang blade!
你的剑术的确很厉害
Your technique is impressive.
但也不足以打败我
But it won't be enough.
我们需要耐心等待最佳时刻来
It's about waiting carefully for the perfect moment to ...
刺
Thrust!
电视
The TV!
为什么你一定要破坏我喜欢的一切
Why must you destroy the things I love?!
挑战者失败  继续吗
Challenger defeated! Continue?
我恨你  我恨你
I hate you! I hate you!
你一点儿都不像珍珠
You're nothing like Pearl!
珍珠很聪明  还总想着保护我远离危险
Pearl is smart, and she always wants to protect me from danger!
而你脑子里只有"和我决斗"
All you want to do is fight me!
接受挑战
Challenge accepted!
行  好
All right, fine!
基础攻击模式已开启
Basic attack mode initiated.
躲  闪  刺
Parry! Parry! Thrust!
-躲  -别在说这些了
- Parry... - Don't say that!
躲  闪  刺
Parry! Parry! Thrust!
击败基础攻击模式
Basic attack mode defeated!
现在开启进阶模式
Now initiating advanced mode!
海象盾牌
Walrus shield.
零食  枕头  绒花  回旋镖
Snacks, pillow, fuzzy flower, boomerang?
回旋镖
Boomerang!
珍珠
Pearl!
我应该乖乖等着你回来的
I should have just waited for you to come back!
我应该乖乖等着
I should have waited for...
最佳时机
...the perfect moment!
飞剑回旋
Boomerang blade!
挑战者胜利  你想再次决斗吗
Challenger wins! Do you wish to duel again?
不要
N-o-o-o-o-o!
史蒂文  我们听到了打斗声
Steven, we heard fighting.
你还好吗  发生什么事了
Are you all right? What's going on?
我只是在拖地
Oh, just mopping.
去死吧
Die!
老实说  我可能是挺想念珍珠的
You know, I might miss Pearl a whole lot,
但有时候  还是应该接受事情本身的发展规律
but sometimes you just have to accept things the way they are
直到你
before you ...
没事了  珍珠回来了
Never mind! Pearl's back!
现在我感觉好多了
That's much better.
噢  很想我吗
Ohh! Hey! Miss me much?
我已经计划好怎么迎接你了
Oh, man! I had this whole thing planned out for when you came back!
史蒂文  你的房间怎么了
Uh, Steven, what happened to your room?
我都懒得管你这事儿了
I don't even want to know what happened to you.
我被飞机撞啦
I got hit by a airplane!
珍珠回来啦
Pearl's back!
史蒂文  你在做什么
Steven, what are you doing?
珍珠回来啦  珍珠回来啦
Pearl's back! Pearl's back!
珍珠回来啦
Pearl's back!
唉  看来我一刻都不能离开你们
Ugh. I can't leave you guys alone for a second.
珍珠回来啦
Pearl's back!